(Alex:)- Yes.
- Half a teaspoon of sprinkles?
- Rainbow.
- Two cherries?
- One on top, one on the bottom.
- Stems removed?
(Alex:)Um... Top one, yes.
I didn't check the one on the bottom.
(Leonard:)Oh!
(Alex:)I'm so sorry, Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)It's all right, Alex. I'm not mad at you.
I'm just disappointed.
Wait, Alex, do you wannajoin us?
(Sheldon:)- Um...
- Alex, a moment.
(Sheldon:)I need a word with Dr. Hofstadter.
(Sheldon:)Do you think it's appropriate
for her to sit with us, given her station?
(Leonard:)Given her what?
(Sheldon:)If I've learned anything
from British television shows on PBS...
(Sheldon:)...it's that servants dine downstairs
with their own kind.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)It's a kindness, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Otherwise, you're cruelly tempting them...
(Sheldon:)...with a glimpse of a world that's just
beyond their soot-stained fingertips.
(Leonard:)Oh, sure.
(Leonard:)- Please join us.
- Oh, okay. Thank you.